Preliminary Guide to the Taintor Family Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Taintor family collection
1668-1869
1720-1869
MS 1256
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
Legal and financial papers, including deeds, wills, estate inventories and receipts relating to families in Branford and Guilford, Connecticut, collected by the Taintor family. The families represented in the papers are Barker, Bishop, Foot, Fowler, Hill, Linsly, Monro, Rogers, Russell, Towner and Tyler.
Taintor family
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mrs. Hope Collins, 1943.
Scope and Contents
Legal and financial papers, including deeds, wills, estate inventories and receipts relating to families in Branford and Guilford, Connecticut, collected by the Taintor family. The families represented in the papers are Barker, Bishop, Foot, Fowler, Hill, Linsly, Monro, Rogers, Russell, Towner and Tyler.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research.
Families; Branford (Conn.) -- History; Guilford (Conn.) -- History; Wills
- Inventory
  Scope and Contents
  The Taintor Family Collection is made up of business, financial, and legal papers concerning various families of Branford and Guilford, Connecticut. The family names involved include Barker, Bishop, Foot, Fowler, Hill, Linsly, Monro, Rogers, Russell, Towner and Tyler. There seem to be no Taintor papers, although one document is annotated by a Charles M. Taintor (Yale 1900S). The papers were donated by Mrs. Hope Collins, of the Taintor Family, in May 1943.
  - Branford
    - Business correspondence, 1791, 1857-1868 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Legal papers, 1668-1869, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Deeds, 1730-1790, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, accounts, estate inventory, 1688-1866, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Guilford
    - Summonses, other legal papers (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Deeds, 1721-1749 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Will, estate inventories, receipts, 1724-1828 (Box 1, Folder 7)